Updated: 21st June 2021 Page 1 of 2

Career Résumé: Brian Dalton, Msc.

solutions@ambervoid.co.uk

http://ambervoid.co.uk

(07767) 273 152

INTRODUCTION

Experienced software developer across the stack in C/C++, Perl, Python, React and more. Years of continuous development on multiple systems with a thirst for knowledge and passion to succeed. Extensive experience in the field overseeing multiple projects, and an excellent team player, previously training up multiple junior developers on advance Perl/jQuery. A visual example of my skills can be seen at http://ambervoid.co.uk.

CURRENT SKILLS

Languages: 10+ years C/C++, Perl, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript. 5+ years Java, PHP. 3 years

in Python, NodeJS.

Databases: 10+ years MySQL

Frameworks: 9 years jQuery. 4 years React, JRX. 2 years Redux..

Systems: Linux, Windows, MacOS, AWS

Source Control & Deployment: 9+ years GIT, Subversion, JIRA, Kanban, Jenkins. 2 years

Kubernetes

QUALIFICATIONS

2009-2010 MSc. Games Programming (Distinction)

University of Hull

Modules taken: Real-time computer graphics, C++ Programming and Design, Advanced Rendering and AI for games, plus others.

2005-2009 BSc. Hons. Computer Science (2:1)

University of Brighton

Modules taken: Computer Graphics Algorithms, 3D graphics and animation, Prog. Lang., concurrency and client-server computing, plus others.

EMPLOYMENT

2021 / Private Company / (Contracted Lead Developer)

Environments: React, Python, MySQL

- Implemented full-stack system for recording sensitive client data

2019-2020 Tag/Williams-Lea International (Contracted Lead Senior Developer)

Environments: Perl, React, ¡Query, MySQL, Python, PHP

- Trained up junior developers - Oversaw previous project completion

- Converted most interfaces to React

2019 *Pixit Media* (Contracted Senior Developer)

Environments: Python

- Automate project deployments - Enhance existing in-house framework

Updated: 7th January 2021 Page 2 of 2

2013-2018 Tag/Williams-Lea International (Senior Developer)

Environments: Perl, jQuery, MySQL, React, Python

- Wrote network optimisation modules Designed & implemented REST APIs
- Wrote front-end UIs updating with JSON Wrote documentation
- Designed databases Continuous integration with agile methods

2008-2009 Accenture (Lead Developer)

Environments: Perl, Linux

- Wrote Project Documents
- Automated application testing
- Oversaw install of SAP database system

REFERENCE(S)

Ross Tredway

Technical Service Manager Tag Williams-Lea Ross.Tredway@TagWW.com (07919) 165 106

Barry Evans

Chief Innovation Officer/Co-founder Pixit Media Ltd. BEvans@PixitMedia.com (07950) 666 248

Christopher Porter

[Personal] <u>ChristopherPorter92@gmail.com</u> (07596) 655 818

Vincent Smith

[Personal] <u>VincentSmith95@Outlook.com</u> (07597) 711 437